24小时
第三季  第一集
快叫医生 救人!
We need medical assistance. Help!
我是保安 坡道口需要增援
This is security, I need help here at the ramp.
长官们 监狱主区一级防范禁闭中
Officers, main blocks are in lockdown.
准备...
Stand by...
可以进了 长官
Go, sir.
请把右手放到扫描屏上
Right hand on the screen.
验证通过
It's clear.
请过来拿回你们的身份证明
Step over there please. I'll give back your IDs.
开1号门
Open 1.
你还好吧 杰克?
You're ok, Jack?
协议签了 我就会好了
I'll feel ok until we get this thing signed.
我不是指那个
That's not what I meant.
人都到齐了
Ok, we are here.
-有什么变动?  -别紧张 杰克 没有大变动
-What kind of change is we're talking about?  -Don't worry, Jack. They're not deal breakers.
他还是得供出一部分恐怖组织名单
He's still gonna give a part of terrorist cells he deals with.
但他想接受二级监禁 而不是最高监禁
He just want to go to a classe 2 detention. Not maximum security.
-你们会满足他的要求吧?  -会的
-And you're gonna give it to him, right?  -Yeah.
我当事人要被带离弗罗里达州 他很不满
My client's not happy that you won't hold him in Florida.
-协议规定他得去明尼苏达州  -让他留在弗罗里达 一样的
-He's getting Minnesota, that's the deal.  -Give him Florida, it doesn't make a difference.
别管到我头上来了好吗?
I let you two do your jobs, why won't let you do mine?
我们不想为了些小事 把问题转移到南部
Because we don't want this thing going South over small detail.
萨拉扎捉摸不透 不知什么时候又会惹麻烦
Salazar is instable, we can't predict what's gonna push his buttons
-实话说: 事情很棘手  -听着 杰克
-and to be frank: there's too much in stake.  -Listen Jack,
我知道你俩用了一年时间才抓到萨拉扎 我深表敬佩
I know you two spend last year getting Salazar and I respect that
-但我得按章办事...  -路易斯 过来一下
-but there's a protocol that I have to follow...  -Luis, come here for a second.
重点不是要看管好他
Putting him away, it's not the point here.
如果他不开口 我们就白忙活了
If he doesn't talk, we haven't accomplished anything.
我花了一年时间 可不仅仅是为了抓个毒贩
I didn't lose a year of my life to arrest some drug dealer.
萨拉扎和全球范围的恐怖组织做过交易
Salazar does business with terrorist cells around the world.
-拿下他们是我们唯一的目标 懂吗?  -我懂
-Bringing them down is our only objective, are we clear?  -I understand.
但你什么都依着他 他会更加得寸进尺
But if you give Salazar everything he asked for, he's just gonna want more.
这是协议 他必须服从
This is the deal and he's going to take it.
但愿你别做错事
You'd better be right.
我现在任由你们宰割?
Is that my life you're holding in your hand?
可以签了
It's ready to be signed.
你在那儿吗 杰克?
Are you in there, Jack?
忘了他吧
Forget about Bauer.
我怎么忘得了那个抓我进来的人? 假装朋友接近我?
How can I forget about the man who put me here? Pretended to be my friend?
我担心你哦 杰克
I'm concerned about you, Jack.
为了抓我 你做的那些事...
The things you did to get me here...
我不想跟别人说
I wouldn't wish on anyone.
面对现实吧 你已不是原来的你
Let's face it, you'll never be the same.
哈! 我也一样
Hey! Neither will I.
我俩在一条船上
So, I guess we are in the same boat.
公开说吧 杰克
I'm about to name names, Jack.
今天对我俩都会意义重大
This is a big moment for both of us.
我太高兴了
That makes me happy,
因为我们被联系起来了
because you see, we are connected now.
也许这是注定的?
I don't know, maybe we always have been?
-我把有变动的地方做了标注  -我不需要看
-I've marked the changes.  -I don't need to see the changes,
我只需要一只钢笔
but I do need a pen.
除非你要我蘸自己的血签字
Unless you want me to sign it with my own blood.
真有趣 我自己的血
It's kind of funny. My own blood.
在哪儿签?
Where do I sign this?
这里
Right here.
作为我的法律顾问 你干得不错
You've done a good job as my counsellor.
但正式地说 还差最后一步
In a go to guy, as they like to say here in States.
我对你坦白过很多事
I think that I own to you
-你得闭上嘴才算尽了职  -什么意思?
-but I don't think you have what it takes to keep your mouth shut.  -What do you mean?
狗杂种!
Son of a bitch!
开门! 开门!
Open the door! Open the door!
快点! 快!
Do it! Now!
快叫医生!
Get a medic in here!
这都是你的错 杰克
This is your fault, Jack.
-接下来就轮到你了  -你想威胁?
-And what happens next is on you too.  -Is that a threat? Is that a threat?
-狗杂种!  -退后! 你先出去!
-Son of a bitch!  -Back off! Take a walk!
你听见了吗?
Did you hear me?
接下来就轮到你了 杰克
What happens next is on you, Jack.
轮到你了!
It's on you!
马切尔医生? 我们照你吩咐隔离了尸体
Dr. Macer? We isolated the body like you asked.
-你说上面有我的名字?  -是 在尸体胸口
-You said my name was on it?  -Yes, it's on his chest.
做个全面检查以防万一
Spread a full panel of tests just to be sure
-我想我们遇到了新型3号类型免疫病毒  -3号类型?
-but I think we're dealing with a new immuno-virus type 3.  -Type 3?
那不正是你们小组正在研究的类型吗?
Isn't that the virus group your team's been doing simulations on?
对 所以才把这个寄给我吧
Yeah, I think that's why this was addressed to me.
通知反恐局了吗?
Has CTU been contacted again?
还没 我们在等你
No, we're been waiting for you.
-你去做初步检测 我去通知指挥官阿尔梅达  -好的
-Go ahead and start the preliminary tests, I'll call Director Almeida.  -All right.
喂! 总统到SC了吗?
Hey! the President arrived at SC yet?
刚到 我们正在安排人手 情报局的已经就绪了
Just about. We're swapping at some of our people now and the secret service is in place.
-他们在等你的评估报告  -好 我打给他
-They're waiting for your resource assessment.  -Alright, I'll call him.
-托尼 上帝知道我受够了!  -怎么了 亚当?
-I've had it Tony, I swear to God!  -What's the problem, Adam?
克萝伊·奥布莱恩没使用我的数据
Chloe O'Brian does not touch my data.
如果外勤组有什么需要 她去问杰克或你 你再告诉我
If field ops wants something, she asks Jack or talks to you, and you tell me.
-她惹麻烦了吗?  -问题不在这儿
-Did she damage anything?  -That's not the point.
我部门之所以做到零故障 是因为我将一切规程做得井然有序
The reason my department has zero down time is because of the procedures I put in place.
-她惹麻烦了吗?  -没有但我...  -行了
-Did she damage anything?  -No, she didn't but I will...  -Go.
杰克管他的部门 我管我的 大家都在同一屋檐下工作 懂吗?
Look, Jack's got his department, I got mine. We are all in the same roof, understood?
很好
Good.
放松点
Now lighten up.
别把自己和别人逼疯了
Don't drive yourself and the rest of us crazy.
好 请稍等
All right, hold on.
卫生部索尼·马切尔医生的电话 还有 有赫尔佐格的消息吗?
Sony Macer from Health services is on the line. By the way, have you heard from Hertzog?
还没有
No, not yet.
放松 米歇尔 你会得到那份工作
Relax, Michelle, you're gonna get the job.
最好是 没有我 你不能去找兰利
It had better, you're not going in Langley without me.
喂! 桑尼 什么事?
Hey! Sunny, what's up?
-很抱歉是坏消息  -什么事?
-This is what I'm really sorry to be right about.  -What are you talking about?
科迪利亚病毒 3号类型的免疫病毒 记得上月的会议吗
Cordella virus, it's a type 3 immuno-virus. Remember last month at the conference,
我提出病毒可能会被培育出来
I raised the possibility a strain could be out there.
-嗯  -说中了
-Yeah.  -Well, it is.
有人扔下了一具感染了病毒的尸体
Someone just dropped out a dead body infected with a virus.
托尼 这些人是玩真格的 他们在引起我们的注意
Tony, these guys are serious. They blew a hole in the door to get our attention.
-这显然是个警告  -警告?
-This is obviously some kind of message.  -A message?
-有人携有病毒并要传播病毒?  -正是
-What? That somebody's got the virus and is willing to release it?  -Yeah, exactly.
-我们需要签发疫情公告吗?  -不 一旦宿主死了 就不再有传染性
-Do we need to issue a quarantine adviser?  -No, once the host is dead, he's not contagious.
帮个忙 查一下地方部门有没有发现类似案例
Right, do me a favour, call the other county facilities and see if there's anymore cases.
好的 怎么查死者身份?
I will. What about the ID on the John Doe?
把你那的所有线索送过来 我们来查
Send everything you have over here. We'll work it up.
-送过去了  -好 谢谢 桑尼
-It's on its way.  -Yeah, thanks Sunny.
什么事?
What is it?
进入一级警戒状态
Initiate the level 1 setting protocol.
-你得闭上嘴才算尽了职  -什么意思?
-And I don't think you have what it takes to keep your mouth shut.  -What do you mean?
萨拉扎想杀沙耶 这3个月他都有机会 却为何选在今天?
Salazar wanted to kill Shaye. He could have done any time in the last 3 months. Why did he pick today?
-他删减了他的要求  -也许 但我不这样认为
-He's cutting his deal.  -Maybe, but I don't think so.
这都是你的错 杰克 接下来就轮到你了
This is your fault, Jack. And what happens next is on you too.
接下来会发生什么?
What happens next?
反恐局
CTU.
我是鲍尔 让阿尔梅达听电话
This is Bauer, patch me through to Almeida.
-喂 杰克  -托尼 你那边有情况吗?
-Hey, Jack.  -Tony, is there anything going on over there?
-我们刚进入警戒状态 这个城市可能受到病毒威胁  -什么情况
-We just had a major protocol come in, possible bio-threat on the city.  -Tell me about it.
一具感染了科迪利亚病毒的尸体 被抛在卫生部门外
Well, a dead body infected with the Cordella virus was left at the Health Services.
估计这只是开端 我们在等人站出来承认此事
We figure it's just a first shoe dropping, we're waiting for somebody to take responsibility.
嗯
Yeah.
-你觉得此事和萨拉扎有关吗?  -不知道
-Do you think that this is connected to Salazar?  -I don't know.
-不知道 也许有吧 我再打给你  -回见
-I don't know. Maybe. Look, I'll get back to you.  -Bye.
-我需要这四个图像的复本  -马上
-I need copies of all four images.   -Right away.
-你好 总统阁下  -韦恩 排演准备好了吗?
-Hello, Mr. President.  -Wayne, are we ready for the run-through?
还差一点 工作组出了点小岔子 我们过几分钟才可以进去
Yeah, almost. The events team dropped the ball so we can't get in there for a few minutes.
-很好  -这可不好 大卫 我开除了朱迪 都是她的错
-That's fine.  -No, no, it's not fine, David, I fired Judy, it was her fault.
-她工作干得不错  -听着 今晚的辩论至关重要
-She's done some good work for, hasn't she?  -Listen, tonight's debate is critical.
她应该检查好每个细节 但她没做到
and she should have had every single base covered but she didn't.
总统阁下 您对今晚同参议员基勒的辩论有何感想?
Mr. President, how do you feel about tonight's debate with senator Keeler?
准备充分 信心十足
Confident, ready to go.
阁下 这是您险遭谋杀后首次重返洛杉矶
Sir, this is your first come back to Los Angeles since the attempt on your life.
-你感到紧张吗?  -一点也不! 洛杉矶是个伟大的城市
-Were you uneasy about coming back?  -Not at all! Los Angeles is a great city.
如果情况允许 我来得还会更早点
We'd be back here sooner if events had allowed it.
重要的是我们在这里 面对未来
What is important, is that we're here now, looking to the future.
感谢各位 下午的正式提问时间 再给你们更多信息
Thank you, that's all for now, a formal Q&A later this afternoon, you'll be briefed.
大卫 我们谈谈审计局的报告 今晚基勒可能会拿这个开刀
David, we've gotta talk about those GAO numbers. I mean Keeler is gonna break it up tonight.
你知道他这个人 我还没...
You know who he is, and I'm just not really...
-大卫 你没事吧?  -我没事
-David, you're all right?  -I'm fine.
-我去叫当地医生  -不用我没事 我等安妮过来
-Let me call one of the resident doctors.  -No, it's all right. I'll wait for Anne.
-你去哪 杰克? 我们谈谈 什么时候可以?  -现在不行!
-Where you're going Jack? We have to talk about this. Then when?  -Not now!
-打给我 我们现在要回反恐局  -为什么?
-Call me. Right now, we've gotta get back to CTU.  -Why?
萨拉扎选在今天杀了沙耶 我们得找出原因
Salazar killed Shaye for a reason. He picked today to do it. We've gotta find out why.
不如我们回去 对萨拉扎严刑逼供?
Fine, let's just go back in here and put the squeeze on Salazar?
他敢当着我们的面杀人 还会怕逼供?
You think he's gonna talk to us after all we just watched him do?
不可能 我们走!
Not a chance. Come on, let's go!
打给我
Just call me.
关于那具尸体 阿尔梅达还说了什么?
Right, so, what else did Almeida say about this dead body?
-杰克!  -嗯?
-Jack!  -What?
我问你托尼还说了些什么?
I asked you about Tony. What else did he say?
他说尸体被抛在卫生部外面 他们正调查死者身份
He said the body was dropped to Health Services, they're trying to ID it.
你从没告诉过我...
You know, you never answered me before...
-你是如何做的? 你知道我在说什么  -你在说什么?
-about how you're doing? You know what I'm talking about.  -What are you talking about?
-我是鲍尔  -杰克 我是克萝伊 那个凯特·华娜想和你说话
-This is Bauer.  -Jack, it's Chloe. I have Kate Warner for you, should I put her through?
好的 接过来吧
Yeah, put her me through.
-杰克?  -你好 凯特
-Jack?  -Hi, Kate.
我找到了你弄丢的那件皮夹克
I just wanted you to let you know I found out that leather jacket you thought you'd lost.
哦! 太好了
Oh! Ok, great.
你看怎么办?
So, what do you wanna do?
我给你送过去 还是寄过去
I can bring it over or send it.
都不用 我会派人去取
No, you don't have to do that. Look, I'll just send someone over to pick it up.
-你确定?  -嗯
-You're sure?  -Yeah.
好吧
Ok, then.
凯特 你好吗?
Kate, how are you?
很难过 我想你
You know, it's hard. I miss you.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really, really sorry.
不用
Don't be.
-保重 凯特  -再见
-Take care of yourself, Kate.  -Bye.
-凯特好吗?  -她很好
-How's Kate?  -She's all right.
-你们还有联系? 抱歉 我不该管闲事  -没有
-So you guys are still talking? All right. None of my business. I'm sorry.  -No, not really.
她只是想还点东西给我 仅此而已
I didn't mean it like that, she's just trying to return a couple thing of mine. That's all.
我想喝水
I need water.
我已叫索尼调查其它部门 有没发现类似病例
I talked to Sony. She's gonna check with other facilities to see if there're anymore cases.
如果有 查出地点
If there are, find out where.
再查所有地区的生化恐怖分子组织
Also let's take regional cells that they have bio-terrorists capabilities
-将他们放在高速处理区  -好
-and put them in the high speed cash.  -Ok.
托尼 拉里·赫尔佐格从兰利打来电话 2号线
Tony, it's Larry Hertzog from Langley on line 2.
喂 拉里
Hey, Larry.
好的
Yeah, we are.
好的 谢谢
Yeah, I will. Thanks.
是关于我的吗?
Is that about me?
是的
Yeah.
他不能给你提供职位 竞选期内资金短缺
He doesn't have a job for you right now. There's no new fund until the end of the election.
我知道了
I see.
还有... 拉里要我在今天内给出答复
Also... Larry told me that he needs an answer from me by the end of the day.
特纳加快了外勤行动
Turner hurried the field post.
你俩都知道自己可以通过 这是重要的职业变动...
You both know you can pass this up, it's major career move...
告诉他你同意
Call him and tell him it's yes.
和我一起去吗? 做为专职妻子...
And you'll come along as the wife? Without a job...
我会陪你到任何地方
I'd go anywhere with you.
只要不用做饭
As so long as I don't have to cook.
亲爱的 只要你答应不做饭 我到哪儿都会带着你
Sweetheart, if you promise not to cook, I will take you with me anywhere.
但他们如果不给你提供职位 我就没有兴趣
But, if they don't have a job for you, I'm not interested.
托尼 国家安全局在1号线
Tony, homeland security on line 1.
稍后再谈吧
We'll talk about it later.
差不多 我要更新数据
Pretty much, I just have to refresh the data on my panel.
-喂! 金? 你做过能力研究吗?  -什么 米歇尔
-Hey! Kim? Have you ever done a capability search?  -Yes, Michelle.
几周前为托尼做过
A couple weeks ago, I had to do one for Tony.
-关于东欧恐怖组织? 很好  -对
-East european cells? Good.  -Yes.
这次不同 是全球恐怖组织
This one it's different. It's gonna be global.
-这是我的密码 谢谢  -我马上做
-Here is my access codes. Thanks.  -I'll be right on it.
喂 亚当! 4号线有DES密码吗?
Hey Adam! Does the link 4 have a DES encryptions?
没 就两个键
No, it's 2 key.
-为什么过滤程序启动了?  -从2到7
-Why is the filter on?  -It's 2 to 7.
-谢谢  -不客气
-Thank you.  -You're welcome.
你是说你想驯服我?
Are you saying you had to break me?
不 是你征服了我
No, it was you who break me.
喂?
Hello?
很好
Good
是
Yes, sir.
好了 收到了 谢谢 克里斯
Ok, it's coming up now. Thanks, Chris.
-亚当 我把这个输入你的系统  -什么东西?
-Adam, I'm piping this over to your system.  -What is it?
卫生部外那具尸体的碎片 我们做个身份分析
Frags on the body that was dropped off at the Health Services. We're doing an ID analysis.
金 能力搜索做到哪儿了?
Kim, where are you on the capability search?
正在进行 还需要15分钟
It's still running, it's gonna be another 15 minutes.
所以你有空?
So, you're open?
是的 需要帮忙?
Yeah, what do you need?
亚当要解析一个身份
Adam is gonna break up a part of an ID.
我们要找出他的姓名
We need a name.
-给他DNA档案  -米歇尔 用不着她帮忙
-Give her the DNA file.  -Michelle, I don't need her help.
用得着 事情很急
Yes, you do. This is urgent.
我准备好了 亚当 把档案发过来
I'm ready, Adam, send the file.
-我有空 亚当 发档案  -我不
-I'm open, Adam, send me the file.  -No.
-这是米歇尔吩咐的  -我不需要别人帮忙
-Michelle just told you.  -I don't need anyone doing my work for me.
-你怎么了?  -这里大家都是靠能力得到工作
-What is your problem?  -My problem is that everyone in this place earned their job.
你是靠老爸得到工作
You got it because of your dad.
这是什么?
What the hell is this?
-翠西 你关了系统? 谢谢  -没有啊
-Tracy, is your system locked? Ok, thanks.  -No, it's not.
可能是你忘了设置群组许可
You know, it could be that you forgot to set the group permission
了解程式的某人换了用户权限
someone who knows the structure and changed the ownership.
不是我 因为我靠老爸找工作 我没啥本事
That wouldn't be me, because I'm incompetent and I only got this job because of my dad.
-把用户权限改回去 金  -把档案发给我
-Change the ownership back, Kim.  -Send the data fork.
米歇尔在等着你出结果
It's your ass Michelle is waiting.
好 我发给你 快解锁我的系统
Fine, I send it. Just unlock my system.
没问题
No problem.
-杰克 我过会儿上去  -好的
-Hey Jack, I'll be up in a minute.  -Ok.
克萝伊 有什么情况
Chloe, give me what you got.
我们和楼下的系统是同步的吗?
Are we in sync with other systems downstairs?
有关尸体的信息在1号盘 我按你要求解密了萨拉扎的信息
Everything Health Services sent on the body is in volume one and I've reprieved all the Salazar information you wanted.
-日期密钥呢? 为什么?  -我没法给你
-Where are the date keys? Why not?  -I couldn't get those for you.
你得找托尼 然后托尼找亚当 然后亚当才会给我
You'll have to talk to Tony, so that Tony can tell Adam, and Adam can give them to me.
-你在开玩笑?  -没有 亚当改动了流程 他恨女人
-You're kidding me, right?  -No, Adam's completely anal about that kind of stuff, and he hates women.
克萝伊 去给我拿密钥 快
Chloe, just get it for me, ok? Please.
把门关上
And close my door.
杰克 我是米歇尔
Jack, it's Michelle.
和卫生部的电话会议要开始了 快下来
The teleconference with Health Services is about to start, you might come down.
-我就在上面听 把线接过来? 谢谢  -好
-No, I'm gonna stay up here. Just pass them through, ok? Thanks.  -Ok.
吓我一跳!
You scared me!
-你在干嘛?  -我... 更新驱动
-What are you doing in here?  -I... am refreshing a drive.
萨拉扎那边怎样?
What's going on with Salazar?
-你当时在场?  -嗯... 太可怕了
-You were there when it happened?  -Yeah... Yeah, it's been crazy.
我爸怎样?
How's my dad taking it?
他很好
He's ok.
太好了
Good.
今天我想和他谈谈
Then, I was thinking about talking to him today.
-今天不合适  -蔡斯 没有哪天是合适的
-Ok, today might not be the best day.  -Chase, no day is a good day.
我们约好交往两个月后没分手 就跟他坦白
We said it that we would tell him if we were still together after two months.
已经三个月了
It's almost three.
为什么不尽快告诉他?
Why don't we just tell him and get it over with?
好吧
All right.
让我去说 好吗?
But I'll do it. Ok?
确定?
Are you sure?
-确定  -真的?
-Yes, I'm sure.  -Really?
真的
Really?
呃 别把驱动放在这儿
Ok, look, you can't put the drive in there,
-我要你查查... 对  -6号?
-what I need you to do is look under... Yeah.  -6, right?
检验结果出来了 托尼 情况不乐观
We just received results of more tests, Tony. Unfortunately, the news isn't good.
这是种武器级的品种
This is a weaponized strain.
-被培育的病毒 致死更快  -有多快?
-The virus has been engineered to kill more rapidly.  -How rapidly?
从解剖情况估计 从被感染那一刻算起
It's a bit of a guess, but based on the autopsy if infection starts at t=0 hours,
有14小时的非传染性潜伏期 14小时后症状出现
there's a non-contagiously latency period of 14 hours. After 14, it presents.
20小时后宿主丧失知觉 24小时后死亡
After 20, the host is incapacitated. By 24, the host is dead.
-病毒的传染性怎样?  -如果一个地区出现此病毒
-What are the epidemiological consequences?  -If the virus initiates in a single location,
1天内会感染数百人
there will be a couple hundred cases by the end of the day 1.
2天后增至数千人
By the end of the day 2, there could be in the thousands.
接下来 感染人数就可以用比例来描述了
But, from there, it's easier to talk about it in percentage of population.
一周后 9%的洛杉矶人口都会被感染
By the end of the first week, 9% of Los Angeles county would be infected.
-那可是一百多万人  -这些人感染上病毒24小时后都会死去
-That's over 1 million people.  -And those people will die within 24 hours of infection.
如果有人要在众人间散播病毒
Right, tell me, if someone is gonna try to release this virus in the general population,
-他会如何去做?  -非常难说
-how would they do it?  -That's a $1 million question.
随处都可以散播
It could come from anywhere.
无法得知什么人 会在什么地方散播病毒
We don't know who has it. There's no way to know where they've planned to release it.
也无法得知散播的方式
We don't even know what form it's in.
嗯 妈
Yeah, 'ma.
蒂姆说他在游泳池等你
Tim wants you to know that he's down at the pool.
呆会儿你能载我去医院吗?
Can you take me to the doctor later on this afternoon?
-爸干啥去了?  -去面试工作 上帝保佑
-What's dad doing?  -On a job interview. Fingers crossed.
让诺尔玛姨妈带你去吧?
Can aunt Norma take you?
嗯? 你有什么重要的事不能载我去?
What? What's so important that you can't take me?
我今天很忙 抱歉 妈
I mean, it's just that I've got a bunch of stuff to do today, 'ma. I'm sorry.
-好吧 我去找诺尔玛姨妈  -谢谢
-Fine, I'll call Norma.  -Thanks.
妈 爱你
Love you, 'ma.
总统阁下 得知有人想刺杀你 举国震惊
Mr. President, the country was in shock after the attempt on your life.
您并无大碍 大家都很放心
But his prayers were answered when it was clear that you would survived.
许多美国人担心你并未完全康复
That said, many americans have expressed concerns that you are not fully recovered
无法胜任接下来4年的任期
and may not be strong enough to serve for 4 more years.
你如何回应这些说法?
How do you respond to those who make such claims?
我每天早上5点起床
I wake up every morning at 5 am.
花1小时呆在休息室
I spend the first hour in the wait room.
一边做运动 一边准备朝会
While I'm exercising, I'm preparing for my morning meetings.
-接下来16小时...  -打住!
-And then, I could in a 16-hours...  -Hold down!
停止录像 重新拍摄 抱歉 恰克 等一等
Could you pause the video please? Get ready to play it back. Sorry, Chuck. Hold on.
别用防御性回答来阐述那个问题
Don't dignify that question with a defensive response.
我不知道陈述事实是防御性的
I didn't realize that stating the facts was being defensive.
对方想谈暗杀问题 好 就让他们谈
They bring up this assassination attempt, fine. Let them.
你提醒大家你的内阁
You remind everyone that it was your administration
不仅抓住了企图谋杀你的人
that had only arrested the man behind the attempt on your life
还揭露了他的组织
but you also exposed his organisation and put a stop to your people way as well.
这些事都是在你"状态不佳"时完成的
All this while you're in this so called "weakened state".
而基勒只是精力好一点! 就这样说
And Keeler would be lucky to have a fraction of your energy! That's what you tell them.
总统先生
Mr. President.
-开始吧 恰克  -妈妈叫他"胆小的兄弟"
-Go ahead, Chuck.  -And mum called him "the timid brother".
-啊! 我的医生来了  -你好  -总统阁下
-Ah! There is my doctor. How are you?  -Mr. President.
-各位 休息几分钟  -我很好 他呢?
-All right everyone. Let's break for a few minutes please.  -I'm fine. How's he been?
-他似乎有点累  -我不累
-He seems a little tired.  -I am not tired.
-只是有点晕  -排练得怎样了?
-Just a little joggled.  -How's this going?
在排练中我肯定赢了!
I'm definitely winning the run-through!
-130/80  -好 我是韦恩·帕默尔
-130/80.  -Good. This is Wayne Palmer.
-累吗?  -没事
-How tired?  -I'm fine.
有一阵子没为你检查身体了 我想...
We haven't done a work upon you in a while and I'd really like...
不 不用检查
No... No... No... No tests.
你总以为我有事 你不检查出来不罢休 但我没事 安妮
You start looking for something, and you don't stop until you find it. I'm fine, Anne.
回华盛顿后 你要做个全面体检
Ok, but when you get back to D.C., I want you to have a complete physical.
-这是医生的命令  -好的女士
-Doctor's orders.  -Yes, ma'am.
安妮 我要和他单独谈谈
Anne, I need him alone for a minute.
好的
So, he's all yours.
-怎么了?  -卫生部打来一个令人担忧的电话
-What is it?  -I just received a very disturbing phone call from Health Services.
洛杉矶卫生部外 发现一具带有极度传染性和致死性病毒的尸体
It seems they found a body here in Los Angeles that's been infected with an extremely contagious and deadly virus.
-看来并非意外事件  -那是什么?
-Now there's concerns this is not just a random occurrence.  -Meaning what?
反恐局正在调查这是否 是一起犯罪活动
Meaning CTU is looking for the possibility that this could be a criminal action.
犯罪活动? 就凭一具死尸?
Criminal action? Based on this one death?
我不清楚细节 大卫 这和尸体被发现的环境有关
I don't know the details David but it has to do with the circumstances in which the body was found.
-留意此事  -好的
-Keep your eye on this one.  -Ok.
-恰克 开始关于国土安全的第7个问题  -好的
-Chuck, can we go on the question number 7 please about homeland security?  -Yes, sir.
-在?  -萨拉扎和检察官的记录呢?
-Yes?  -Where is the transcript of Salazar and the D.A.?
我发到你电脑里了 在你的文件目录中
I sent them to your system, it's in your directory.
见鬼 我不想存在目录里 我希望它和其它萨拉扎资料放在一起!
Damn it, I didn't want it in my directory, I wanted it stored with the rest of the files from Salazar!
好的 我照办
Ok, I'll do it.
克萝伊 要是你不能一次性把事情办好 我就换一个能做好的
Chloe, listen to me. If you can't start getting things right the first time, just let me know because I can get someone else who can.
我能做好 如果你想把它和其他文件放一起 你就该事先告诉我
I did do it right. If you wanted it with the other files, you should have said so that it isn't standard so I wouldn't think of doing it in that way, would I?
现在起照我的方式做! 好吗?
Just do it that way from now on! Ok?
我不会读心术 杰克 有要求你得说明白
I can't read minds, Jack, you've just gonna have to spell it out for me,
否则我们的工作关系...
otherwise this relationship won't...
见鬼 克萝伊! 快去干活!
Damn it, Chloe! Just do it now!
好吧
Fine.
-喂 杰克  -干嘛?
-Hey Jack.  -What?
-刚才怎么了?  -帮我换掉克萝伊
-What was that about?  -I need you to replace Chloe for me.
-换掉? 但她是最棒的分析师  -她哪有 她太慢
-Replace her? But she's the best analyst we got.  -No, she's not. She's slow.
她不慢 她有些古怪 但精通业务
She's not slow. I mean, she may be a little weird but she knows her stuff.
你状态很糟
You look like hell.
你说我什么?
What did you say to me?
我们处在警备状态? 不知你是否会失控
Well, we're in actif protocol, ok? And I need to know if you're up for it or not.
蔡斯 我喜欢你 你是个不错的孩子
I like you Chase, you're a nice kid.
但不许到我办公室那样对我说话 懂吗?
But don't you ever come in my office and talk to me like that again. Do you understand me?
我只是说你情绪焦燥
I'm just saying you're on edge. Ok?
你这是在无故开除克萝伊
I mean, come on man, you're about to fire Chloe for no reason.
克萝伊 抱歉刚才对你发火 我只是情绪不好
Chloe, I'm sorry I took your head off. I was just in a bad mood. Ok?
你满意了?
You're happy?
杰克 我还有件事要告诉你
Look Jack, there's one more thing I've gotta talk to you about.
好的 我们马上下来
Ok, we'll be right down.
萨拉扎有情况
They got something on Salazar.
你想告诉我什么?
What do you wanna tell me?
没啥 以后再谈
Nothing. It will hold.
好
Good.
为了防范安全疏漏 现在起我们每天进行检查
So, in order to plug any possible security breaches, we're doing day checks from now on.
最长8小时做一次工作记录...
Break your logs into 8 hours or less...
说了吗?
Did you tell him?
没 现在太忙 但我保证会说的
No, there's a lot going on right now. It will happen, I promise.
10分钟前有人给FBI打了匿名电话
An anonymous phone call just came in FBI by 10 minutes ago.
都来听听
We're getting into this right now.
-你听过吗?  -嗯
-Did you hear it?  -Yeah.
-准备就绪  -播录音
-Ok, it's ready.  -Bring it up.
你们收到了我们寄的东西 并知道我们拥有3号型肺部病毒
I know you received our package and realize we're in possession of a type 3 pulmonary immuno-virus.
仔细听着 我们的要求很简单
Listen very carefully to these instructions. Our demand is very simple.
6小时内释放拉姆·萨拉扎
We want the release of Ram Salazar in the next 6 hours.
如果拒绝 病毒就会散播到人群中
If you refuse to comply, the virus will be unleashed to the general population.
就像你们专家说的一样 你们没时间阻止病毒的传播
As your experts will tell you, you would not have time to stop its spread.
稍后再通知你们交人的细节
Details how Ram is to be delivering will follow.
-就这些  -知道电话来源吗?
-That's it.  -Do we know where the phone call originated from?
不清楚 信号从卫星转来
We don't know yet. It came from a scrambled satellites,
我们正在缩小范围
you know. We're trying to narrow it down.
杰克 你最了解萨拉扎 你估计此人是谁
Jack, you know Salazar better than anybody else here. Who do you think we're dealing with?
肯定是他兄弟 二把手赫克托
Without a doubt his brother. Hector was next in command.
拉姆被收押后 他迅速躲了起来
He went underground the second Ram was taken into custody.
我知道萨拉扎在南美和墨西哥有大量财产
Now look, I know for a fact that the Salazars own multiple properties in South America and Mexico
虚设公司 注册了资金
registered under dummy corporations.
可惜 现在墨西哥政府也找不到他们
Unfortunately, right now, the Mexican government, it seems they can't locate them.
所以我们只能撒大网 追踪电话来源
So we've gonna to throw out a pretty large net to try and trace the origin of that call.
-我们会努力的  -对了 死者身份查到了吗
-Right, we'll work on it.  -Ok. How are we doing with the ID on the dead body?
-米歇尔正在分析DNA  -指纹和牙齿呢?
-Michelle is working on the DNA.  -Ok. What about prints and dental?
没牙齿 没指尖
No teeth, no finger tips.
必须找出死者身份 这是追查对方活动的唯一线索了
Ok. Look, we need this ID. This's the only hook we've got into their operation.
-萨拉扎审得如何?  -完全是浪费时间 他很强悍
-What about questionning Salazar?  -Complete waste of time. This is a man without vulnerability.
用刑对他不起作用
He doesn't respond to physical interrogation,
他也不在乎别人的死活 包括他的子女
and he doesn't care about another living soul including his own children.
托尼 发现一个符合死者的身份
Tony, we've a match on John Doe.
米歇尔 有何发现?
Michelle, what did you get?
死者叫大卫·戈斯 洛杉矶东部的街头毒贩 也卖些小道消息
The dead body is a David Goss. He's a street dealer in east L.A., also an informant.
看来他逃脱了几次 禁药局也一年多没管他了
It looks like he flips sides some many times DEA stopped working for over more a year ago.
-知道他最后去过哪儿吗?  -我们正在查
-Do we have a last known address?  -We're working on it.
我们要弄清谁让戈斯感染病毒
Ok. We're gonna need to know who infected Goss.
找出最后几周和他接触过之人的名单
You've gonna to work up a list of everyone who's being involved in this life over the last weeks.
好 我们齐心协力从这儿入手查案
All right. We'll pull together everything we got hands on.
好 同时也要从萨拉扎的毒品网络入手
Ok, but work it from the other side as well, go through Salazar network.
看是否能找到戈斯的毒品供应者 好好干
See if you can find this supplier who sold to Goss. Good work.
跟我来 蔡斯 看能不能从赫克托这发现什么
Chase, come with me. We'll see if anything is coming on Hector.
为什么让我爸帮你干这活儿? 这不是他的工作
Why do have my father doing this kind of work for you? It's not his job.
就今天
It is today.
为什么要杀沙耶?
Why did you kill Shaye?
看看周围 拉姆
Take a look around, Ram.
这里是美国监狱 还没上法场你的屁股就会坐烂
You're in an U.S. prison where your ass is going to rot until you're executed.
想改善条件吗? 那就老实交待
You want to improve your condition here? You'd better start talking to me.
-交待什么?  -为什么要杀你的律师?
-What do you want to talk about?  -Why did you kill your attorney?
我不想让他告诉你们
I didn't want him talking to you.
-告诉什么?  -所有一切
-About what?  -About anything.
你很不爽?
It's eating at you, isn't it?
那你还等什么
What am I up too?
来吧路易斯 我被拷着 这俩看守马上可以把我打得满地找牙
Come on, Luis. You have me in chains. Two tough guys waiting for a chance to beat me to a pop.
来吧 路易斯! 看看用刑能不能逼我开口!
Do it, Luis! See if you can me beat it out of me!
真不好玩儿
You are no fun.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
你怎么了?
What's wrong?
我父亲是个农场工头
My father is a ranch foreman.
你答应过不让他卷入你的那些勾当
You promised me he wouldn't be involved in your other activities.
我付给你父亲三倍薪酬
I pay your father 3 times more than usual.
不! 我答应到这住 但条件是不让父亲和弟弟 沾上你那不干净的生意
No! I told you when we came to live here that I didn't want him or my little brother to be exposed to your illegal business.
你食言了 赫克托
You broke your word, Hector.
你伤害了我
And that hurts me.
我很难过
It hurts.
-对不起 克劳迪娅 我会补偿你的  -怎样补偿?
-I'm sorry Claudia, please I'll make it up to you.  -How?
我让你爸休假 再多付一个月资金
I'll give your father some time off, an extra month pay.
这就是你解决问题的方式? 用钱...
That's your solution to every problem, isn't it? Money...
-给FBI打过电话了吗?  -打过了
-Have you made the call to the FBI?  -Yes, I did.
嗯... 我们的猎物呢?
And... what about our boy?
-我在监视他  -仔细监视
-I'm watching him now.  -Keep him close.
是
I will.
在提华纳做事是什么感觉?
So, what was it like to get knee deep in some fine Tijuana tale?
-我在那儿做事  -什么意思?
-I did not do that.  -What do you mean?
我并没有去那儿 我被解雇了
I mean I didn't go down there to get laid.
-但你说...  -是的... 我说过
-But you said...  -I know... I know what I said.
为了以防万一 有些事我没告诉你
I just didn't wanna tell you in case something happened.
有什么秘密?
What's the big secret?
-记得高中同学扎克·帕克吗?  -嗯
-You remember Zach Parker from High school?  -Sure.
去年他不是因为贩毒被学校开除了吗?
Didn't he get busted last year for dealing coke?
总之 他设计让我认识那男人
Whatever, he set me up to this guy from there.
-设计? 你怎么认识他的?  -我就是认识他! 好吗?
-What do you mean he set you up? How do you even know him?  -I know him! Ok?
你都干什么了老兄? 卖麻药?
What are you into here man? You're selling dope?
准确说不是...
No, not exactly...
准确说你干嘛了?
So exactly what are you doing?
那人付了我五千美元 帮他把毒品带入境 就在昨天
This guy, he payed me $5000 to bring some coke over the border. I did that last night.
今天我把毒品送过去 又挣了五千美元
Today, I drop it off. I get another $5000.
-你疯了吧  -就一次
-You goota be out of your mind.  -This is one time.
-过境可不容易 但还是做到了  -你为什么这么做?
-Getting over the border was the hard part. It's already done.  -Why are you doing this?
我妈要做透析 我爸失业了
My mum is under dialysis, my dad is out of a job.
我们要被房东赶出这鬼地方
We're about to get evicted from this crappy appartment.
-懂了吗?  -你彻底疯了
-Is that good enough for you?  -You are seriously insane.
蒂姆 今天我还会去干一笔
Look Tim, I'm about to make this drop later today.
-我想... 也许我们可以一起干...  -不行! 休想!
-I was just thinking maybe... maybe you and I, we could go together...  -Forget it! No way!
你在车里等 我去送毒品 再回来 就这么简单
You wait in the car. I go in, I make the drop, I come back, and that's it. There's no big deal.
我不感兴趣
I'm not interested.
考虑一下嘛
Think about it.
-FBI什么时候接到的电话  -20分钟前
-When did FBI get this call?  -About 20 minutes ago.
不知道谁打来的?
And we don't know who we're dealing with?
来电声音经过了处理 电话只说
It was a scrambled voice on an open line. All we know is what he said.
如果不交出萨拉扎 就散播病毒
They want Salazar or they're gonna release the virus.
你怎么想 韦恩? 取消辩论?
What's your take on this, Wayne? Do we cancel the debate?
目前 国防部和反恐局建议提高警戒级别...
So far, DOD, the Pentagone and CTU have recommended raising the alert level but...
也在商量我们是否该继续留在洛杉矶
they are discussing whether or not we should stay in Los Angeles.
-总统阁下  -什么?
-Sir.  -Yes, sir?
帕卡德医生来了 她想见你
Doctor Packard is here, she's asked to see you.
-告诉她我很忙  -是 阁下
-Tell her I'm busy please.  -Yes, Mr. President.
亚伦 等等 带她来见我
Aaron, wait. Tell her I'll speak with her.
你现在要去见她?
You really wanna do that right now?
是的 韦恩
Yes, Wayne, I do.
什么事 安妮
Yes, Anne.
吃这个药 早晚各一片
I want you to start taking these. One on the morning and one before you go to bed.
帮你恢复精力
It will help your energy.
我说了我没事
I told you I was fine.
你是说过 你不相信医生了?
I know what you told me. Are you gonna trust your doctor or not?
我信
Of course, I am.
怎么了? 你看起来很烦恼
What's going on? You seem upset.
没事 这段时间天天都这样...
Nothing. It's just gonna be another one of those days...
什么意思?
What does that mean?
我得过去工作了
I've got to get back.
-好吧  -下次聊
-Ok.  -We'll talk later.
-这系统怎么了?  -什么?
-What is wrong with this system?  -What?
网格无法显示
The grid won't come up.
你需要一个控制通路
Because you need a control access.
现在还在导航界面
You're still on navigation.
谢谢
Thank you.
把它传到我办公室好吗?
Look, can you just patch it through to my office?
-他今天怎么了?  -没事
-What's his problem today?  -Nothing.
这时间表没用 记录从12月直到2月
This timeline does not make a sense, it goes straight from December to February.
你想干嘛 杰克?
What are you trying to do, Jack?
解决问题 你也该试试
Same thing you should be trying to do. Solve this problem.
我不是指这个
That's not what I'm talking about.
听着 杰克
Listen Jack.
老实对你说
I'm gonna be honest with you.
我尊敬你
I look up to you.
如果有必要我愿意为你而死 但现在坦白说
I'd take a bullet for you if I had to but right now I'm gonna hold the mirror up.
你接近萨拉扎有6个月
You were under of Salazar for 6 months.
我知道他们对你做了什么
I know what they did to you.
我知道你对自己做了什么
And I know what you did to yourself.
你无法短时间摆脱那些事
You can't make that go away over night.
你以为我不知道吗?
You think I didn't know?
这不关你的事 蔡斯
You should mind you own business, Chase.
我想告诉你
All I'm trying to say
我来是为你工作
is that I'm here for you.
但今天不是你向大家证明你更强大的日子
But today is not the day to try to prove to everybody that you are better.
这会对你产生不利影响 你我都清楚
It's about to hit hard, you know that and I know that.
做回以前的自己吧
So do what you've gotta do, man.
调整好自己 我们才能展开工作
Get your head straight, so we can do our work.
爸 你在上面吗?
Dad, you're up there?
爸?
Dad?
嗯
Yeah.
我能上来吗? 我有事要告诉你
Can I come up? I need to talk to you about something.
现在不行 孩子 我正在处理东西
Not right now, sweetheart, I'm in the middle of something.
好吧 有空打给我
Ok, well call me when you have a few minutes.
好
Ok.